l have spent my whole life
trying to bring order to the universe...
(Sheldon:)...by carefully planning
every moment of every day.
(Sheldon:)But all my efforts, our dinner schedule,
my pajama rotation...
(Sheldon:)...my bowel movement spreadsheet...
(Sheldon:)It's clear now,
l've been wasting my time.
(Leonard:)Good. I'm taking that disgusting chart
off the fridge.
(Howard:)You know...
(Penny:)...sometimes it's nice
not knowing what's coming.
(Penny:)Look at me and Leonard.
We went out, broke up,
trying again.
(Penny:)We don't know what's gonna happen.
(Sheldon:)Oh, please, everyone knows
what's going to happen.
(Sheldon:)But I see your point.
l think this could be good for you.
(Leonard:)Maybe it's time for you
to shake things up a bit.
(Sheldon:)You're right.
l should embrace the chaos.
- Great. What are you gonna do first?
- l don't know.
l could do anything. All bets are off.
(Sheldon:)The world is my oyster.